Guide to the Office of the President Records, Sarah Gibson Blanding Files, 1911-1977 (bulk 1946-1964)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Gifts, 1926-1969
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding Scholarship Fund, 1963-1964 (Folder 15.5)
  - Mabel Maxwell Brace Scholarship, 1951-1954 (Folder 15.6)
  - Virginia Swinburne Brownell, 1947-1949 (Folder 15.7)
  - Gertrude Buck Fund, 1929-1950 (Folder 15.8)
  - Jane Breckir Scholarship Fund, 1962-1967 (Folder 15.9)
  - Carillonic Bells, 1955 (Folder 15.10)
  - Eleanor Dodge Child Fund, 1960 (Folder 15.11)
  - Chicago Hall, 1955-1960 (Folder 15.12)
  - Agnes Rindge Claflin Art Purchase Fun, 1965-1966 (Folder 15.13)
  - Class of 1967 Senior Gift, 1967-1969 (Folder 15.14)
  - Colgate-Palmolive Company College grants, 1956 (Folder 15.15)
  - Connecticut General Life Insurance Aid to Higher Education, 1964 (Folder 15.16)
  - The Danforth Foundation, 1947-1959 (Folder 15.17)
  - George Sherman Dickinson Chair, 1956-1965 (Folder 15.18)
  - The George Sherman Dickinson Scholarship Fund, 1956-1957 (Folder 15.19)
  - Lilla Thomas Elder and Caroline B. Dow Scholarship Fund, 1955-1960 (Folder 15.20)
  - Lucy Kellogg English Prize, 1926-1957 (Folder 15.21)
  - Esso Education Fund, 1956-1967 (Folder 15.22)
  - Experimental Theater (Safe), 1966-1967 (Folder 15.23)
  - Ferrell House, 1954-1959 (Folder 15.24)
  - Mary Davis Firestone Memorial Scholarship, 1960-1963 (Folder 15.25)
  - Ford Motor Company — Incentive Donation Program, 1960-1967 (Folder 15.26)
  - Ford Foundation, 1964-1966 (Folder 15.27)
  - French Corridor Prize, 1946-1966 (Folder 15.28)
  - General Electric Educational and Charitable Fund, 1954-1967 (Folder 15.29)
  - General Motors College Scholarship Plan, 1955-1967 (Folder 15.30)
  - Robina Knox Gregg Scholarship, 1954-1961 (Folder 15.31)
  - Carroll W. Griffin Memorial Fund, 1959-1960 (Folder 15.32)
  - Elizabeth Hazelton Haight Fund, 1952-1954 (Folder 15.33)
  - Huber Family (J. M. Huber Corp. and family contributions), 1955-1967 (Folder 15.34)
  - Kayden Gift, 1963-1967 (Folder 15.35)
  - Molly Thacher Kazan Fund, 1964 (Folder 15.36)
  - Sara and Felicia Lamport Prize Fund, 1943-1952 (Folder 15.37)
  - Margaret S. Lewisohn Fund, 1954-1956 (Folder 15.38)
  - Low-Cost Housing Unit, 1948-1950 (Folder 15.39)
  - Rebecca Lowrie’s Gift (Farm), 1965-1967 (Folder 15.40)
  - Mary Ann Richardson Lukens Scholarship, 1961-1967 (Folder 15.41)
  - MacCracken Chair of English Literature, 1945-1967 (Folder 15.42)
  - Main Building (Renovation), 1953-1961 (Folder 15.43)
  - Mary Conver Mellon Chairs in Art and History, 1961-1963 (Folder 15.44)
  - Mary Conver Mellon Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1948-1964 (Folder 15.45)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corp., 1956-1967 (Folder 16.1)
  - Mabel Newcomer Fund, 1958-1961 (Folder 16.2)
  - Anna Margaret During Noyes Memorial Fund, 1930-1952 (Folder 16.3)
  - Emma Hartman Noyes House, 1939-1967 (Folder 16.4)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary Salary Fund (Pittsburgh Project), 1958 (Folder 16.5)
  - Cark G. Parrish Memorial Fund, 1965-1966 (Folder 16.6)
  - Margaret C. Peabody Fellowship in international Relations, 1950-1951 (Folder 16.7)
  - Mabel Pearse Scholarship Fund, 1949-1952 (Folder 16.8)
  - Pittsburgh Endowment, 1960-1967 (Folder 16.9)
  - Alice Katharine Plum Memorial Fund, 1949-1950 (Folder 16.10)
  - Poughkeepsie Community Day Gifts and Pledges, 1961-1964 (Folder 16.11)
  - Presser Foundation, 1954-1967 (Folder 16.12)
  - Procter and Gamble Scholarship Program, 1955-1966 (Folder 16.13)
  - Helen Gates Putnam Fund, 1941-1968 (Folder 16.14)
  - Sarah Tod Fitz Randolph Scholarship, 1950-1966 (Folder 16.15)
  - Helen Dwight Reid Educational Fellowship, 1964-1966 (Folder 16.16)
  - Ellen H. Richards Memorial Fund, 1944-1966 (Folder 16.17)
  - Doris A. Russell, 1962-1964 (Folder 16.18)
  - Lucy Maynard Salmon Chair of American History, 1949-1966 (Folder 16.19)
  - Lucy Maynard Salmon Fund for Research, 1949-1967 (Folder 16.20)
  - Shell Companies Foundation, 1958-1967 (Folder 16.21)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1954-1966 (Folder 16.22)
  - Standard Oil Company of New Jersey, 1954 (Folder 16.23)
  - The Joseph F. Stein Loan Fund, 1957-1961 (Folder 16.24)
  - Elizabeth Drinker Storer Memorial Fund, 1949-1950 (Folder 16.25)
  - Gifts (Summer Institute), 1954-1958 (Folder 16.26)
  - Summerfield Scholarship Fund (Solon E. Summerfield Foundation), 1955-1967 (Folder 16.27)
  - Mona Taggart Memorial Scholarship, 1946-1962 (Folder 16.28)
  - Eva March Tappan Scholarship, 1930-1954 (Folder 16.29)
  - Mary Rogers Thomas Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1956-1963 (Folder 16.30)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy — Mary B. Poppenheim Scholarship Fund, 1952-1960 (Folder 16.31)
  - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop, 1947-1967 (Folder 16.32)
  - Nancy Leob Weal Fund, 1962 (Folder 16.33)
  - Elizabeth Stillman Williams Fund, 1954-1963 (Folder 16.34)
  - Woods Hole Table, 1947-1949 (Folder 16.35)
  - Potential Donors, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 16.36)
  - Annuities, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 16.37)
  - Life Income Contracts, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 16.38)
- Series V. Within the College, 1941-1969
  - Annual Reports (1), 1946-1947 (Folder 17.1)
  - Annual Reports (2), 1946-1947 (Folder 17.2)
  - Annual Reports, 1947-1948 (Folder 17.3)
  - Annual Reports, 1948-1949 (Folder 17.4)
  - Annual Reports, 1949-1950 (Folder 17.5)
  - Annual Reports, 1950-1951 (Folder 17.6)
  - Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Folder 17.7)
  - Annual Reports, 1952-1953 (Folder 17.8)
  - Annual Reports, 1953-1954 (Folder 17.9)
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1955 (Folder 17.10)
  - Annual Reports, 1955-1956 (Folder 18.1)
  - Annual Reports, 1956-1957 (Folder 18.2)
  - Annual Reports, 1957-1958 (Folder 18.3)
  - Annual Reports, 1958-1959 (Folder 18.4)
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1960 (Folder 18.5)
  - Annual Reports, 1960-1961 (Folder 18.6)
  - Annual Reports, 1961-1962 (Folder 18.7)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1963 (Folder 18.8)
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1964 (Folder 19.1)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1963-1964 (Folder 19.2)
  - Academic Freedom (Vassar College), 1952 Feb – 1953 Jun (Folder 19.3)
  - Vassar College Academic Freedom (Barenblatt Case), 1954 (Folder 19.4)
  - Academic Freedom (Vassar College), 1953 Jul – 1954 Jun (Folder 19.5)
  - The Freeman Magazine (Correspondence with students and parents re articles) (McCarthyism), 1952 (Folder 19.6)
  - The Freeman Magazine (correspondence with people without college re articles) (McCarthyism), 1952-1953 (Folder 19.7)
  - The Freeman Magazine (General Correspondence) (McCarthyism), 1952-1953 (Folder 19.8)
  - The Freeman Magazine (correspondence with alumnae re articles in) (McCarthyism), 1952-1953 (Folder 19.9)
  - Replies to S.G.B. letter about Biological Sciences, 1962-1963 (Folder 19.10)
  - Biological Sciences — Early History of Consolidation, 1960-1961 (Folder 19.11)
  - Biological Sciences — Active Candidates, 1962-1963 (Folder 19.12)
  - Chapel Tower Room Dedication, 1950 Apr 26 (Folder 19.13)
  - Field Work Committee, 1958-1961 (Folder 19.14)
  - Vassar Community Church (correspondence with Mr. Pike), 1947 May – 1950 Aug (Folder 19.15)
  - Vassar Review Story — Controversy with Catholic Church, 1949 (Folder 19.16)
  - Vassar Review Story — Correspondence with Aronin and Editors, 1949 (Folder 19.17)
  - Vassar Review Story — Correspondence with Trustees, 1949 (Folder 19.18)
  - Vassar Community Church Conference, 1949 May (Folder 19.19)
  - Vassar Community Church, 1943 Oct – 1946 Jun (Folder 19.20)
  - Feasibility Study for Punched Card Equipment, 1961 Dec (Folder 19.21)
  - D.P. Students (Displaced Persons), 1949-1952 (Folder 19.22)
  - Applied Work in Social Sciences (Carnegie Grant), 1950 May – 1953 Jun (Folder 19.23)
  - Field Work in Social Sciences, 1953-1955 (Folder 19.24)
  - Flags, 1952 (Folder 19.25)
  - Mellon Foundation (General), 1959-1960 (Folder 19.26)
  - Mellon Foundation (General), 1958-1959 (Folder 19.27)
  - Mellon Foundation (Publications), 1959-1960 (Folder 19.28)
  - Mellon Foundation — Budget, 1958-1959 (Folder 19.29)
  - Trustee Sub Committee on Mellon Fund, 1962 (Folder 19.30)
  - Memorial Minutes, 1954-1961 (Folder 19.31)
  - Pensions for Faculty and Employees, 1944-1947 (Folder 19.32)
  - Bureau of Publications, 1941 Aug – 1946 Jun (Folder 19.33)
  - Questionnaires, 1953-1955 (Folder 19.34)
  - Questionnaires, 1955-1958 (Folder 19.35)
  - Questionnaires, 1958-1960 (Folder 19.36)
  - Questionnaires, 1960-1961 (Folder 19.37)
  - Questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Folder 19.38)
  - Renaissance Conference, 1956 Mar (Folder 20.1)
  - Research Assistants employed on grants from N.S.F. and Public Health Service, inc., 1961-1962 (Folder 20.2)
  - Salary Scale, 1949-1953 (Folder 20.3)
  - Faculty Salary Scale, 1958 (Folder 20.4)
  - Salary Data — Surveys, 1957 Jul 1 – 1958 Jun 30 (Folder 20.5)
  - Faculty Salary Scale — Changes in Scale, 1946-1959 (Folder 20.6)
  - Social Security (possible extension), 1949 Feb – 1951 Jan (Folder 20.7)
  - Three-Year Plan, 1944-1946 (Folder 20.8)
  - Tuition, 1951-1958 (Folder 20.9)
  - Vassar Summer Institute, 1954-1955 (Folder 20.10)
  - Vassar Summer Institute, 1956 (Folder 20.11)
  - Vassar Summer Institute (Policy Committee), 1956-1957 (Folder 20.12)
  - Vassar Summer Institute, 1957 (Folder 20.13)
  - Vassar Summer Institute, 1958 (Folder 20.14)
  - Vassariana, undated (Folder 20.15)
  - Assistant to the President, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.16)
  - Auditors, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.17)
  - Biology — Plant Science, Zoology, Physiology, 1960-1962 (Folder 20.18)
  - Biological Science Building Architects, 1964 (Folder 20.19)
  - Biological Science Building, 1955-1958 (Folder 20.20)
  - Biological Sciences — Applicants, undated (Folder 20.21)
  - Biological Sciences, 1960-1963 (Folder 20.22)
  - Boots and Saddles, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.23)
  - Chicago Hall, 1963 (Folder 20.24)
  - Civil Defense, 1962-1963 (Folder 20.25)
  - Clippings, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.26)
  - College Assemblies, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.27)
  - College Council, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.28)
  - College Government Association, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.29)
  - College Research Center, 1962-1964 (Folder 20.30)
  - Committee of Correspondence, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.31)
  - Cresap, McCormick and Paget Study of Business Organization, 1964 (Folder 20.32)
  - Faculty Children Tuition, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.33)
  - Field Work Committee, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.34)
  - Foreign Students, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.35)
  - Freshmen Discussion Group, 1962 (Folder 20.36)
  - Dr. Henry Noble MacCracken, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.37)
  - Mellon Foundation — General, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.38)
  - Memorial Minutes, 1962 Jul 1 -; (Empty) (Folder 20.39)
  - Miscellany News, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.40)
  - Non-Western Cultures, 1962-1964 (Folder 20.41)
  - Owl and Torch, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.42)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.43)
  - Officer of Public Relations, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.44)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1963-1964 (Folder 20.45)
  - Research Assistants Employed on Grants from NSF and Public Health Service Inc., 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.46)
  - Questionnaires, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.47)
  - Questionnaires, 1963-1964 (Folder 20.48)
  - Registration, 1955-1964 (Folder 20.49)
  - Registration, 1963 (Folder 20.50)
  - Registrations (Dead Wood), 1963-1964 (Folder 20.51)
  - Renaissance Seminar in Italy, 1962-1963 (Folder 20.52)
  - Faculty Salary Scale, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.53)
  - Library Salary Scale, 1962 (Folder 20.54)
  - Salary Data Surveys, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.55)
  - Secretary of the College (Mrs. Brownell’s letters), 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.56)
  - Secretary of the College, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 20.57)
  - Senior Chapel, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.1)
  - Senile Seniors, 1962 (Folder 21.2)
  - Social Events, 1963-1964 (Folder 21.3)
  - Sophomore Fathers Weekend, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.4)
  - Student Employees in the President’s Office, 1963-1964 (Folder 21.5)
  - Student Inters, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.6)
  - Student Intern Program — United Nations, 1964 (Folder 21.7)
  - Student Internship Program — Federal, 1962-1964 (Folder 21.8)
  - Student Internship Program — Washington, 1962-1963 (Folder 21.9)
  - Summer Use of the Campus — General, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.10)
  - Summer Institute in Earth Science, 1963-1964 (Folder 21.11)
  - Summer Institute in English, 1964 (Folder 21.12)
  - International Summer School of Nursery School Association of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, 1962-1963 (Folder 21.13)
  - Educational Television, 1963 (Folder 21.14)
  - TIAA — CREF, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.15)
  - Travel Plans, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.16)
  - Tuition, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.17)
  - Vassar College Vassariana, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.18)
  - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop, 1964 (Folder 21.19)
  - Vassarion, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 21.20)
  - SOC 28/a, 1968-1969 (Folder 22.18)
  - Art Department Annual Reports, 1959-1964 (Folder 22.19)
- Series VI. Associations, 1932-1964
  - American Association of University Professors, 1939-1960 (Folder 21.21)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1960 – 1963 (Folder 21.22)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1961-1964 (Folder 21.23)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1938-1955 (Folder 21.24)
  - Fund for Adult Education (Executive Committee), 1950-1954 (Folder 21.25)
  - Ford Foundation — General, 1951 Mar – 1952 Dec (Folder 21.26)
  - Ford Foundation — Vassar College Approach, 1951-1954 (Folder 21.27)
  - Ford Internship Instructors, 1953-1955 (Folder 21.28)
  - Ford Foundation — Faculty Fellowships — VC, 1951-1954 (Folder 21.29)
  - Ford Foundation — Research in Public Affairs Grant, 1959-1962 (Folder 21.30)
  - Ford Foundation Grant for Research in Public Affairs, 1962-1966 (Folder 21.31)
  - Ford Grants for Public Research — Forms, undated (Folder 21.32)
  - Ford Foundation (General), 1957 Jul 1 – 1959 Jun 31 (Folder 21.33)
  - Ford Foundation — Study, 1961 (Folder 21.34)
  - Ford Foundation — A Ten Year College Budget, 1961 (Folder 21.35)
  - Ford Foundation — A Profile of Vassar College, 1964 Jan (Folder 21.36)
  - Ford Foundation (College Grant’s Program), 1955-1957 (Folder 21.37)
  - Ford Profile, 1963-1964 (Folder 21.38)
  - S.G.B.’s Official Ford Profile of Vassar College, 1954-1974 (Folder 21.39)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1958 Mar (Folder 21.40)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1932-1955 (Folder 21.41)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1963 (Folder 21.42)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1963 (Folder 21.43)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1958-1960 (Folder 21.44)
  - Danforth Study Group, 1962-1964 (Folder 21.45)
  - Empire State Foundation — Poughkeepsie Area Solicitation, 1959-1960 (Folder 21.46)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1938-1962 (Folder 21.47)
  - Mid-Hudson Area College Presidents, 1961-1964 (Folder 21.48)
  - Seven College Conference Minutes, 1937 Feb – 1951 Jun (Folder 22.1)
  - Seven College Conference, 1959-1960 (Folder 22.2)
  - Seven College Conference, 1960-1961 (Folder 22.3)
  - Seven College Conference, 1961-1962 (Folder 22.4)
  - Seven College Conference, 1962-1963 (Folder 22.5)
  - Seven College Conference, 1963-1964 (Folder 22.6)
  - National Scholarship Program of Seven College Conference, 1954 Jul 1 – 1955 Jun 30 (Folder 22.7)
  - Seven College Conference (General), 1955 Jul 1 – 1957 Jun 30 (Folder 22.8)
  - Seven College Conference (General), 1957 Jul 1 – 1958 Jun 30 (Folder 22.9)
  - Seven College Conference, 1951–1953 (Folder 22.10)
  - Seven College Conference, 1953-1954 (Folder 22.11)
  - Seven College Conference (General), 1954 Jul 1 – 1955 Jun 30 (Folder 22.12)
  - Seven College Conference, 1946 Jul – 1948 Jul (Folder 22.13)
  - Seven College Conference, 1948 Jul – 1951 Jun (Folder 22.14)
  - Seven Colleges — Approaches to Foundations, 1947-1953 (Folder 22.15)
  - Seven Colleges — Approaches to Foundations, 1953–1954 (Folder 22.16)
  - Seven College Conference Minutes, 1951–1958 (Folder 22.17)
- Series VII. Centennial, 1956-1971
  - 100th Anniversary Committee Commemorative Catalogue, 1956-1957 (Folder 23.1)
  - 100th Anniversary Committee (extra copies of Commemorative Catalogue material), 1956 (Folder 23.2)
  - S. G. Blanding — Vassar Chronology, 1960 (Folder 23.3)
  - 100th Anniversary (Director), 1959-1960 (Folder 23.4)
  - Development Group (Approaches to Foundations for International Conference), 1959-1960 (Folder 23.5)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — Central Committee, 1961 (Folder 23.6)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Central Committee, 1959-1960 (Folder 23.7)
  - Centennial Loan Exhibit, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.8)
  - Centennial Opera, 1957-1962 (Folder 23.9)
  - Vassar Commemorative Stamp (Centennial), 1959-1961 (Folder 23.10)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Mid-Nineteenth Century Festival, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.11)
  - 100th Anniversary — Miss Rukeyser’s Play, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.12)
  - Alumnae Day, 1961 Jun 10 (Folder 23.13)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Contemporary Arts Conference, 1961 (Folder 23.14)
  - 100th Anniversary — Academic Convocation, 1961 (Folder 23.15)
  - 100th Anniversary — Charter Day and Charter Day Party, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.16)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Dorothy Stickney Performance, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.17)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Documentary Film, 1961 (Folder 23.18)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — Natural and Social Science Conference, 1960 (Folder 23.19)
  - Community Day, 1961 May 6 (Folder 23.20)
  - 100th Anniversary Centennial Opera, 1960-1962 (Folder 23.21)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary (International Conference), 1960-1961 (Folder 23.22)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — International Conference, 1958-1960 (Folder 23.23)
  - 100th Anniversary Celebration — International Conference, 1957-1958 (Folder 23.24)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary (Publications Committee) — Chronology, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.25)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — Publications Committee, 1958-1960 (Folder 23.26)
  - 100th Anniversary Committee — Publications Committee, 1956-1958 (Folder 23.27)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary (Director), 1960-1962 (Folder 23.28)
  - Post-International Conference — Correspondence with participants, 1961-1962 (Folder 23.29)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — General, 1959-1960 (Folder 23.30)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — General, 1958 Jul – 1959 Jul (Folder 23.31)
  - 100th Anniversary Committee, 1956 Jul – 1958 Jul (Folder 23.32)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary Committee Minutes, 1957 (Folder 23.33)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary — General, 1960-1961 (Folder 23.34)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary (General), 1961-1962 (Folder 23.35)
  - At Vassar: The First Century, 1961 Jan (Folder 23.36)
  - Centennial Office Television and Radio Report, 1960 Jul (Folder 23.37)
  - Centennial — Programs, undated (Folder 24.1)
  - Centennial — Intra-Mural, Sciences Conference, Festival of the Mid-19th Century, 1960 (Folder 24.2)
  - Centennial — Inquiries about, 1971 (Folder 24.3)
  - Vassar College Centennial — Pamphlets and Broadsides, 1960-1961 (Folder 24.4)
  - Vassar College Centennial — Alumnae Festival Documents and Pamphlets, 1960-1961 (Folder 24.5)
  - International Conference Papers, 1961 Mar (Folder 24.6)
  - Science Conference Papers, 1961 (Folder 24.7)
  - Vassar College Centennial — Alumnae Magazine, 1960 Oct – 1962 Oct (Folder 24.8)
  - Centennial — Central Committee, 1959-1961 (Folder 24.9)
  - Centennial — Central Committee, 1956-1959 (Folder 24.10)
  - Mathew Vassar Lecture Fund — Records, 1962-1963 (Folder 24.11)
  - International Conference of the Centennial — Minutes, 1957-1961 (Folder 24.12)
- Series VIII. Additions, 1943-1977
  - Herbst Weber, Isabelle ex’58, 1958-1961 (Folder 25.1)
  - Flora Maull, 1944-1959 (Folder 25.2)
  - Student Misconduct [Confidential], 1961-1962 (Folder 25.3)
  - Note from English Thesis — Students, 1961 (Folder 25.4)
  - Correspondence - A, 1951-1968 (Folder 25.5)
  - Correspondence - B, 1946-1967 (Folder 25.6)
  - Correspondence - C, 1952-1968 (Folder 25.7)
  - Correspondence - D, 1951-1967 (Folder 25.8)
  - Correspondence - E, 1954-1967 (Folder 25.9)
  - Educational Associations, 1959-1968 (Folder 25.10)
  - Educational Institutes — College, Institute, School, University, etc. (SUNY Separate), 1961-1969 (Folder 25.11)
  - Correspondence - F, 1952-1969 (Folder 25.12)
  - Foundations — Applications to, 1953-1967 (Folder 25.13)
  - Correspondence - G, 1958-1967 (Folder 25.14)
  - Correspondence - H-I, 1951-1969 (Folder 25.15)
  - Correspondence - J, 1966 (Folder 25.16)
  - Correspondence - K, 1955-1967 (Folder 25.17)
  - Correspondence - L, 1959-1968 (Folder 25.18)
  - Correspondence - M, 1958-1969 (Folder 25.19)
  - Correspondence - N-O, 1953-1968 (Folder 25.20)
  - New York — University of the State of, 1952-1968 (Folder 25.21)
  - Correspondence - P-Q, 1951-1969 (Folder 25.22)
  - Questionnaires, 1954-1969 (Folder 25.23)
  - Correspondence - R, 1950-1968 (Folder 25.24)
  - Correspondence - S, 1955-1968 (Folder 25.25)
  - Correspondence - T, 1957-1963 (Folder 25.26)
  - Correspondence - U-V, 1949-1967 (Folder 25.27)
  - Correspondence - W-X-Y-Z, 1956-1969 (Folder 25.28)
  - Survey of Student Activities, 1951 (Folder 25.29)
  - Feasibility Study for Punched Card Equipment, 1961 Dec (Folder 25.30)
  - Economic Feasibility of Consolidation of Food Service Facilities, 1962 (Folder 25.31)
  - Survey Report of Food Services, 1964 (Folder 25.32)
  - Inauguration, 1946 (Folder 26.1)
  - Correspondence re N.Y. Vassar Club Speech, 1961 Mar 18 (Folder 26.2)
  - Secretary of the Faculty, 1946-1950 (Folder 26.3)
  - Advisory Committee, 1943 Aug – 1946 Sep (Folder 26.4)
  - Advisory Committee, 1946 Sep – 1950 Jun (Folder 26.5)
  - Committee on Assessment, 1955-1956 (Folder 26.6)
  - Committee on Conference with the Trustees, 1951-1959 (Folder 26.7)
  - Committee on Conservation, 1947-1954 (Folder 26.8)
  - Coordinating Committee, 1951-1953 (Folder 26.9)
  - Reports of Augmented Curriculum Committee, 1946 (Folder 26.10)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1950-1952 (Folder 26.11)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1952-1953 (Folder 26.12)
  - Endowment Group (Minutes), 1950 Feb – 1954 Jun (Folder 26.13)
  - Endowment Group, 1950-1954 (Folder 26.14)
  - Endowment Agents, 1954 (Folder 26.15)
  - Endowment Group, 1954-1957 (Folder 26.16)
  - Endowment Group — Minutes, 1954-1957 (Folder 26.17)
  - Development Committee, 1957-1958 (Folder 26.18)
  - Development Group Minutes (Endowment Group), 1957-1958 (Folder 26.19)
  - Development Group, 1958-1959 (Folder 26.20)
  - Development Group Minutes, 1958-1959 (Folder 26.21)
  - Committee on Faculty Procedure, 1946 Jun (Folder 26.22)
  - Committee on Fellowship Graduate Study, 1944-1950 (Folder 26.23)
  - Committee on Foreign Study, 1947-1949 (Folder 26.24)
  - Committee on Housing, 1945-1949 (Folder 26.25)
  - Joint Planning Committee, 1947 (Folder 26.26)
  - Joint Committee (Faculty and Students), 1947 Mar 22 (Folder 26.27)
  - Committee on Research, 1943-1953 (Folder 26.28)
  - Committee on Revision of Governance, 1946-1951 (Folder 26.29)
  - Committee on Salary Scale (Faculty), 1950-1952 (Folder 26.30)
  - Committee on Salary Scale, 1955-1956 (Folder 26.31)
  - Committee on Size of the College, 1954-1955 (Folder 26.32)
  - Faculty Committee on Social Museum, 1946-1949 (Folder 26.33)
  - Committee on Veterans, 1946-1949 (Folder 26.34)
  - Committee on Work Load, 1949-1950 (Folder 26.35)
  - Report: Cresap, McCormick, & Paget, "Survey of Administrative Activities - Vassar College,", 1951 Jun (Folders 26.36-26.37)
  - Faculty investigations by the U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, 1953-1957 (Folder 26.38)
  - U.S. Presidents, inaugurations and memorials, 1963-1965 (Folder 26.39)